[choking]
[stab in back]
[gasping for air]
Matteo!
Come on! Come on,
we must be so close now.
- Come on.
- I've lost too much blood.
I...
No, come on. You can
do this, you can do this!
Argh...
Ok.
I'm gonna find help.
Shit...
Oh, come on.
Come on...
Shit!
[gasps]
Get away from him.
[muffled dialogue]
What are you saying?
I can't hear...
[distant church bell]
Matteo? Matteo...
I feel a lot better.
Weird.
On your feet.
The bells...
Yes.
There is life in Libitina.
Let's go!
[distant church bell]
[church bell]
Everybody will be
inside for Sunday Mass.
We need to warn them.
Matteo, wait.
I want to tell
you something.
I don't remember how
we met or what we did.
I just...
... remember waking
up with you.
... and
I'm really glad we did.
Same.
The souls of the just men
and women
must be cleansed by
temporary punishment.
To be admitted into
the eternal country.
[doors opening]
Even the least pains in purgatory
are greater than what ever pain
is imaginable in the world.
The final purification
of the elect after death.
Matteo...
Nonna?
Matteo, wait!