Ok.
Let's get out of here.
[gasping]
One new video message
from 'Clifford Hendricks'.
Matteo, slow down a sec.
- Zan!
- Hey Zanna!
So we are
walking home.
I didn't get the tattoo in
the end, but guess what?
I got this instead...
Sexy as fuck.
Right?
So listen, I
just wanna say -
I love you.
Even though I never get
to see you anymore because
you're, I don't know,
busy breaking the internet.
But...
... you deserve that success.
- Tell her.
- You do, you really do.
- She does, doesn't she?
- Yeah.
Stay on the grind, sis!
Oh, and no hard feelings
about the money.
Tough love, like, I get it.
[laughs]
Who's the party boy?
My brother, Cliff.
He's one of those
unfalteringly positive people.
You know the type.
He'll go far.
... and you aren't positive?
No, I am when I
need to be.
Come on, pick
up the pace.
Your earphones stayed in?
Yeah, I forget they're
in half the time.
I'm the brand's ambassador.
I get five figures
every time I say
they're the best sports
earphones money can buy.
Nice.
Nonna!
What the fuck is
wrong with you?!
You trying to
get us killed?!
Sorry.