Ok.
Let's get out of here.
[gasping]
One new video message
from 'Clifford Hendricks'.
Matteo, slow down a sec.
- Zan!
- Hey Zan!
Yo, so we are
riding home.
Well, I didn't get the
tattoo in the end but
we got these instead.
[laughs]
So, listen. I just
want to say - I love you.
Even though, like, I
never get to see you anymore
because, like, you're
busy breaking the internet.
But you deserve
that success, right?
Stay on the grind, sis.
Oh and thank you so
much for the money.
As you can
see, we are
riding home in style
thanks to you.
- Woo!
Who's the party boy?
My brother, Cliff.
He's one of those
unfalteringly positive people.
You know the type.
He'll go far.
... and you aren't positive?
No, I am when I
need to be.
Come on, pick
up the pace.
Your earphones stayed in?
Yeah, I forget they're
in half the time.
I'm the brand's ambassador.
I get five figures
every time I say
they're the best sports
earphones money can buy.
Nice.
Nonna!
What the fuck is
wrong with you?!
You trying to
get us killed?!
Sorry.