Miri, play me something
for motivation.
... and keep it low.
Sure, resuming
'Motivate The State' podcast.
But how could you change
your mindset so absolutely?
Well, I started
as a teenager.
I eliminated my dependence on
the validation of others.
Hold up. I'm gonna play
some music so this goes viral.
- ♪ cinematic music ♪
- I repurposed my natural instincts.
I took my self-doubt as a challenge,
an obstacle to overcome.
Some people can
reinterpret their nerves
as excitement, even in the
face of failure or danger.
Alright Zanna, give
me some advice.
I always have to speak my mind
when I disagree with something.
Well, until you have the perfect
response. Hold your tongue.
But then I look weak.
Well, there's a difference
between looking weak
and looking stupid.
Listen. Analyze.
Wait.
... and when the time is right.
[gunshot]
Risk it all!
[blood spurts]
[earphone music continues]
[sheep bleating]
♪ Italian music playing ♪
Help!
Zanna?!
Inside!
What's happened?!
Inside! We need
to get inside.
Ok. Ok.
Come on!
Sit down.
[panting]
I'm Matteo.
Yeah, I know.
I remember you.
Just like you remembered
me this morning.
Yeah, that hot pink
running gear's hard to miss.
[chuckles]
I'm not cold.
You will be.
The wind gets
in up here.
Stay here.
- Wait Matteo, where are y--
- I'll be right back.
[ticking clock]
[door closes]
Lock that door.
Fits you nicely.
Sorry, I was just
getting some firewood.
I didn't mean to...