Miri, play me something
for motivation.
... and keep it low.
Sure, resuming running playlist.
♪ 'Baddie' by King Future x DEVMO ♪
[gunshot]
[blood spurts]
[earphone music continues]
[sheep bleating]
♪ Italian music playing ♪
Help!
Zanna?!
Inside!
What's happened?!
Inside! We need
to get inside.
Ok. Ok.
Come on!
Sit down.
[panting]
I'm Matteo.
Yeah, I know.
I remember you.
Just like you remembered
me this morning.
Yeah, that hot pink
running gear's hard to miss.
[chuckles]
I'm not cold.
You will be.
The wind gets
in up here.
Stay here.
- Wait Matteo, where are y--
- I'll be right back.
[ticking clock]
[door closes]
Lock that door.
Fits you nicely.
Sorry, I was just
getting some firewood.
I didn't mean to...