Hi.
Oh! Thank you.
I mean... grazie.
Ciao.
Oh. Ciao!
Hopefully that'll
cure a hangover.
Please be legal...
A very good morning, everybody.
How are you?
Please excuse the mess
that is my face.
I haven't slept because
I've been traveling all night.
This week's 'Run Diary' is
gonna be a goddamn special one!
Because I am
celebrating reaching...
Drum roll, please...
[Drum roll sound]
Five million followers!
And it's all thanks
to you guys.
So, I have travelled
to the Veneto...
... or 'Veneto' region
of Northern Italy.
And let me
tell you something.
The drive from
the airport alone,
was absolutely breathtaking.
One minute, I was
driving along Lake Garda
and the next minute,
I was on Monte Baldo.
And now, I am in this little
remote village called Libitina,
which is world-famous
for its running trails.
So guys, I am gonna
finish getting ready
and do something about this.
... and I'm gonna catch
you on my running trail.
[blows kiss]
Bye.
Good morning, Zanna.
I see you are
in a new location.
Do you need navigation?
Not today, Miri.
Awesome.
Ciao.