Look, I know how
much she means to you.
But we got to be clever,
and we got to be careful, ok?
Yeah, of course.
You're right.
So, was your nonna
always into fitness?
Yeah.
She played sports
with me all my life.
Ate healthy, too.
My nonna, not so much.
Smoking got him.
Sorry.
She kept begging
him to stop and...
... well, in the end,
she was right.
As always.
I am sorry.
But your nonna, she
sounds like my kind of girl.
Come on.
Hey, I got a confession.
What is it, Zanna?
Don't be weird.
It's not a Catholic thing.
I just need the toilet.
We just came
from the farm.
So? It is what it is.
Well, we can't go back.
We can go through the woods,
or there's an old military battery
with a proper toilet just beyond
the perimeter, if you prefer.
All right, well, which one's
on your nonna's route?
Well, she uses
both, but uh,
it's best we
don't split up.