[slap impact]
Ow.
You shouldn't sneak
up on people like that.
Where's your key?!
There's no crime around here.
What? So, how do
you lock the doors?
- I don't.
- What?
Wanna tell me
what's going on?
Yeah, I borrowed some
of your wife's clothes.
[chuckles]
My wife?
Yeah, I didn't think
she'd mind.
Don't worry, your
secret's safe with me.
No, those are
my nonna's clothes.
I told you about
her this morning.
Anyway, why would
you need them?
Because mine made me
look like a big pink target.
Where is your nonna?
She went for a run.
Matteo, I am running
from a killer.
[chuckles]
Your nonna is
in serious danger.
Nothing bad ever
happens out here.
Look, I don't know
what's going on either.
You want me to run into
the woods and leave you here alone.
What the fuck would I
steal from a farm, you idiot?!
Matteo!
Matteo, you have
to believe me.
Show me proof!
Ah!
Just wait...
Holy shit, guys.
This is turning into
a mass murder.
The road manager
and his wife...
You see?
I don't see any killers.
Are you fucking serious?!
Obviously, I didn't do this!
Please leave, Zanna.
What?
I said, leave!
Matteo, where are you going?!
Matteo!
Listen to me.
Shit...
Inside.
Get inside!
Hey!
Yeah, come this way!
Shit!
[BLANK_AUDIO]