Guys, I've got places
to be and very little time.
Sorry.
[phone rings]
Oh, shit.
[groans]
Hey.
I've been trying you
for the past hour, Zanna.
You know it's
past my bedtime.
Yeah, well, signal's
shit out here.
What?!
Weren't you supposed to
fly home directly from Thailand?
I took the scenic route.
You know you have
a scheduled meeting
with a competition
winner, right?
One of those
underprivileged, terminally ill,
whatever kids. You know
what I'm talking about.
Oh, shit.
Sorry.
I totally forgot.
- Yeah.
- Well, I can't do anything in person.
So...
Hm.
Yeah, yeah.
I know you.
That's why I
scheduled a video call.
The kid's on the
other line, please take it.
Ah, Brian!
I'm begging you
to take this call.
We don't want the charity or the
parents complaining to the press.