[gunshot]
[belt jangling]
[groans]
Oh my god...
♪ Italian music playing ♪
Could your belt
be any janglier?
Yeah, sorry.
[chuckles]
It was my nonno's.
I started wearing it
after I took over the farm.
Mm.
Or did you want...
...morning sex?
No.
I've got to conserve
my energy.
Right, yeah.
I figured.
[nervous laugh]
Ah! I got my nonna this
set for her birthday.
You can spot it a mile off.
You've mentioned both
your grandparents
while angling for morning sex.
Shit.
Sorry, Zanna.
You remembered my name.
Thanks for last night.
Um.
There's not a lot of
people to do that without here.
Did you have a good time?
[laughs]
Do you want feedback?
Oh my god, Matteo.
Hey, you remembered
my name too.
Well, only the locals
call me Matteo, though.
I was 'Matt' back home.
So, if you want
to call me that.
Or... Matteo works.
You know...
Either.