[BLANK_AUDIO]
You always wanted
to be a vlogger?
Not exactly.
I was a really
good youth runner,
but I wasn't the best.
What?
... and you need
to be the best?
Yeah, of course.
So, I pivoted to
online health and fitness.
Now I'm just a few million followers
away from being the best.
Must take a lot of discipline
to film your every move.
Yeah, good Catholic discipline.
You're Catholic too?
Not so much now, but
the discipline was instilled
- in me at a young age.
- By who?
Sorry, you probably
told me all this last night,
but I don't remember a thing.
Didn't realize I
got that wasted.
Yeah, me either.
Although, I have an excuse.
Jet lag and a six and a
half hour drive to get here.
So, you're a
role model, huh?
[laughs]
I guess.
It feels weird
saying that out loud.
But I've never really understood
why somebody would follow
somebody who can do
something that they can't.
But it is what it is, and if I
don't do it, somebody else will.
Well, keep going.
Someday you might be able
to retire out here in Libitina.
[laughs]
Yeah.
So, what about you?
You're not into social media?
Nah, signal's shit out here.
There's no point.
Why don't you just leave?
You're too young to
be here anyway.
I chose to be here.
Yeah, but why?
Obligation to your grandparents?
No, I wanted
to better myself.
Work on that Catholic discipline.
Jesus, your nonna
must have had
ankles of steel to
run this every day.
So listen, this is
slightly awkward but
are you so Catholic that
you didn't use a condom last night?
Uh...
I don't know.
Jesus, why can't
we remember?
Who lives there?
Just a crazy old guy.
No red mark.
- Nonna might be in there.
- Easy, tiger.
We just passed
two corpses in a car.
Yeah, they were
killed hours ago.
What?
When you left my place
this morning, you left by road.
You would have passed
that car on your way home.
I go a different way.
Really?
Because there's only
one road on the map.
Yeah, I go off-road.
I helped you kill
one of them, Zanna.
Shit.
God, I don't know
what to believe anymore.
[gunshot]
Get down!
Shit!
Oh god...
[gunshot]
Winchester 243.
The rifle.
I can hear it.
It holds five rounds.
You've got a few
seconds between shots.
[gunshot]
Go!
[gun reload]
Shit.
[gunshot]
Oh, whoa, whoa!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
I'm just a runner.
Who did I shoot?
Tell me!
I don't understand...
Uh...
American.
My friend... he's hurt.
He needs medicine.
Do you have
any medicine?
Ok...
[pained grunting]
Ah! Che cazzo!
Calm down.
You're wasting 12 year old single malt
on a traitor and a coward.
What did he say?
Just insults.
I told you he's crazy.
You're lucky my bullet
skimmed past you.
[pained chuckle]
Tell him-- listen.
Next, I'll pull that
bolt out of you--
No.
It's pierced my lung.
I'll suffocate on my own
blood if you pull it out.
What happened to you?
I was leaving for a morning hunt...
He says an attacker shot him
and left him to die like an animal.
Which one was it?
What colour was their mask?
It was...
... white like bone.
Do you have a landline?
A telephone that
we can call for help?
They cut the phone line.
The hunter became
the hunted.
I'm going to
die a cliche...
... but I've got one bullet
left for that bastard.
One bullet is enough.
You are from Libitina.
Everyone here knows
how to beat death.
Trust someone who served
this country for 40 years.
The reaper comes
for us all.
No matter how
fast or far...
... you run.
Ok, listen.
Tell him...
When we get back to Libitina,
we're going to send help. Ok?
- Let's go.
- Wait, wait. You can't leave him.
What are you talking about?
He doesn't want our help.
But it's wrong.
It's wrong?!
He's got a gun.
Better in here
than out there.
He's got a gun
with one bullet.
Better than none.