It's Matteo.
I came for you!
I'm sorry, Matteo.
Our souls must suffer
and do good works
that break us of attachments
of sin and self.
Wake up!
This...
... is the word of God.
Matteo!
My brave boy.
What's happening?
I found you...
... hanging in the barn.
In this moment,
you are on a middle plane.
Purgatory?
A place which offers salvation
and purification...
... in the form of a test.
It is a test you
have passed.
Yeah, come this way!
Thanks to your actions here,
you have purged
your venial sin of
[gunshot]
Cowardice.
You shall now...
... ascend.
... and Zanna?
She too has been tested.
To purge her soul
[gasping]
of her venial sin...
Selfishness.
[gasping]
[crowd cheering]
... and?
Has she done
enough to be saved?
No, my treasure...
She failed the ultimate test.
No, no, no...
She's a good person.
Ah, yes?
Then why...
... did she abandon you?
Cliff?
Cliff!
No, no, no, Cliff.
Cliff, wake up.
No, no, Cliff.
Come on. Wake up.
My beautiful baby brother.
Cliff, you were right.
Life is to be lived.
You have principles
but not rules.
... and you don't hold back,
but you're never out of control.
[ambulance siren]
... and you're kind.
You're so, so kind.
Wake up!
Cliff...
I am going to give you one
last motivational speech, ok?
You listen to me.
Keep fucking fighting.
Keep fighting because
you deserve more time
to spread your amazing energy.
So, keep going.
Keep fighting. Please!
[tearful]
Wake up, I love you.
Please...
Please.
I love you.
Wake up!
[crying]
Cliff?
No, no, no...
Cliff?!
What have you
fucking done?!
done with him?!
Please...
Give him back...
[flesh pierced]
[spluttering]