Yeah...
You're right.
Sorry for holding us up.
It's all right.
We should get going.
[sighs]
[panting]
Come on.
I'm so sorry. It's my fault.
I shouldn't have stopped.
It's fine.
He would've stabbed
us both. He was fast.
Come on.
Come on!
[heavy panting]
All right. I can't keep
up the tough guy act.
Please, can we rest?
Ok...
Ok... but just
for a minute.
[panting]
You've always
been a strong Catholic?
Not always.
I'm trying to improve.
I'm a coward.
Come on.
You're not a coward.
You were a soldier. You wear
those stupid boots all the time.
I was discharged
with dishonor.
Why?
Desertion.
It haunts me every day.
I'm sorry.
I really need something
for this pain.
Try these...
These are herbs
from the mountain.
They only grow here.
Well, are they any good?
Never tried them.
Now's as good
a time as any.
We've stayed too long.
Time to go. Come on.
Watch it. Watch it!
Shit!
Go!
Move!
Quickly.
Down here.
Go, go, go.
Argh!
I need more
of those herbs.
Shit...
Here.
Finish them.
Swallow it!
Ok, good.
Let's go!
Zanna...
Stay here.