Hey!
[screams]
[strong impact]
[grunting]
[screams]
[piercing sound]
[panting]
That was my nanno's.
Been busted for years.
Damn.
Is this him?
Yeah.
They both gave
their all for me.
Now I'm out here just
trying to do the same for them.
A rosary?
You're Catholic, huh?
Mm-hm.
I'm a stronger believing
now than before.
Really?
Put it on.
We need all the
help we can get.
We don't know how many
of those fuckers are out there.
Doesn't matter.
I'm finding my nonna.
Do you always do
everything in those boots?
Pretty much.
I'm ex-army.
Even running?
Yeah.
We'd run for miles in these.
Fair enough.
So, what route does
your 'nanna' usually take?
Well, there's no 'usual'.
Sometimes she takes the
north trail, sometimes the south.
She says 'hello' to
her friends in Libitina.
Then she takes the other
trail on the way back home.
So which trail
did you take?
The south.
But I didn't see
any sign of her.
Then we'll take
the north trail.
So, how long does
she usually take?
Six hours.
She's fast for 85.
Jesus.
No wonder she features
so heavily in your pillow talk.
[door opens]
- Zan!
- Hey Zanna!
So we are
walking home.
Well, I didn't get
the tattoo in the end.
But guess what?
I got this instead...
Sexy as fuck.
So listen, I
just wanna say -
I love you.
Even though I never get
to see you anymore because
you're, I don't know,
busy breaking the internet.
But you deserve that success.
- Tell her.
- You do, you really do.
- She does, doesn't she?
- Yeah.
Stay on the grind, sis!
Oh, and no hard feelings
about the money.
Tough love, like, I get it.
[laughs]
Who's the party boy?
My brother, Cliff.
Watch your step...
He's one of those
unfalteringly positive people.
You know the type.
He'll go far.
... and you aren't positive?
Yeah, when I need to be.
Come on, let's
pick up the pace.
Your earphones
have stayed in.
Yeah, I actually forget
they're in half the time.
I'm an ambassador
for the company.
I get five figures
every time I say
they're best sports
earphones money can buy.
- Nice.
- Mm-hmm.
Nonna!
What the fuck
is wrong with you?!
You trying to
get us killed?!
I'm sorry.