Yeah, fine. It's
not about the charity,
it's not about the parents,
it's about the kid, right?
Let's go!
Thank you. You're a saint.
The kid's name is Jovan.
Got it.
Hey Jovan!
Are you there?
What's up, Zanna?
Where are you?
I'm on a run!
That's awesome!
You're my hero.
Aw, that's super sweet.
Like, I mean it.
Ask anybody.
My family, my friends.
This poster was the only
birthday present I got this year.
Aw, you didn't
want anything else?
Well...
I wanted the Zanna Hendricks
t-shirt and hat and
sweatbands and sneakers, but...
... this poster was all
my mom could afford.
Ok well, I have an idea.
How about I send you
all those things, my treat?
Seriously?
Seriously. Legends
like you are why I do this.
You're the best.
No, you are, and I've
got one more piece of advice
for you, Jovan. Stay focused
and listen to your mom, ok?
Of course.
Thank you, Zanna.
[calming exhale]
- [bolt flies past]
- Ah!
What the f...
- [bolt flies past]
- Ah!
[panting]