[sighs]
I'm sorry.
Hi.
Can I give
you a hand?
Thanks.
Where?
Over there.
♪ Italian music playing ♪
- Okay.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
But you are
not from Libitina.
[laughs]
How did you guess?
No, I'm just passing through.
Your village is very beautiful.
We people stay beautiful too.
Mm.
All live here 80, 90, 100 years!
I heard.
So, tell me,
what's your secret?
Is it the great olive oil,
the good wine?
Simple.
We live for each other
and respect the land.
When you run,
you will see.
We care for nature
and buildings from our past.
A real sense of community.
Yes.
But I have another
little secret...
We make love every day.
[laughs]
More or less.
[chuckles]
Okay.
I'll save some bottles
if you survive your trail.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
- Take care.
[phone ringing]
Zan!
Oh my god.
Yo, guess what?
I just popped a Xan,
and now I am talking to--
What is it, Cliff?
I'm running.
I thought you were
kickboxing in Thailand?
No.
That finished two weeks ago,
and it was muay thai.
Keep up, Cliff.
Right, so where
are you now?
Italy.
Thought I'd take a
pit stop on the way home.
[laughs]
Slow down.
Burnout's a real thing.
[buzzing noise]
What's that noise?
Is that a tattoo gun?!
Yeah, so what do you
think would look better?
Um.
Tribal? Arabic?
Cliff, you're wasted.
You are gonna be paying
penance with your life
if you get a tattoo. Mom
and Dad are going to kill you.
There's that trusty
Catholic guilt-tripping again.
Relax. Jocelyn's the
only one getting one.
Who's Jocelyn?
- A girl.
- No shit.
Don't get her name tattooed...
or mine... or yours,
for that matter.
Joce is a huge
fan, by the way.
Say 'hi', babe.
[gasps]
Oh my god...
Zanna, you kicked ass
in Thailand, queen.
Thanks.
I've got a new 'Run
Diary' dropping tonight.
Oh, bet.
I'll be watching.
[laughs]
Do you use
me to get girls?
- Of course.
- Hey! Shut up!
Ok.
Um.
So, is that why
you called me?
No.
So, just give
me one sec.
Ok, I'll be right
back, babe.
Stay strong.
Those stars are so unique.
Could you wire
me some cash?
Shit's a little
expensive out here.
You mean drugs
are expensive.
Cliff, you're supposed
to be studying.
Well, I'm nailing
my grades anyway.
Come on, Zan.
Life's to be lived, you know?
We're all going
to die someday.
- Would you rather--
- Save it.
Ok, so... the cash?
[sighs]
I mean... I promise...
I'll never ask again.
It's just so I can
get through this date.
Please.