Yeah, ok.
But this is about the kid,
not about the charity or the parents.
Thank you.
You're a saint.
Yeah, I know.
- The kid's name is Grace.
- Got it.
Hey, Grace!
[heavy breaths]
Zanna Hendricks!
Hey.
How are you?
A lot better
now you're here.
Sorry I'm sleepy.
I stayed up
to meet you.
Aww, I hear you're a big
fan. I'm on this amazing run.
You are gonna love it.
It's gonna be my best one yet.
I'm so excited!
You've taught me
to keep positive
and I've gotten stronger.
Well, I'm always
there for you.
I want to start
running soon but...
... the doctors are
telling me 'no'.
Where are you now?
Well, I'm just on a
break at the moment
but I'm gonna get
right back into it.
Cool.
... and who's that
behind you?
Uh. I will catch
you soon.
It was so nice
talking to you.
Thank you so much, Zanna.
[door creaks open]
[calming exhale]
- [bolt flies past]
- Ah!
What the f...
- [bolt flies past]
- Ah!
[panting]