The trail is the only
certainty we have.
Keep your eyes open.
Come on.
Ok.
Ok, listen to me.
Pain is just a sensation
that your brain creates
to tell your body
something's wrong.
You just need a
distraction, that's all.
Um...
Oh, you can
answer a riddle.
Ok, I've got one. Um...
What keeps you young?
- What? That's it?
- Yeah. Come on.
Um...
Travel?
No.
Oh God. Love?
Experiences?
No, not even close.
Come on.
I give up.
No, no, no.
Don't give up. Come on.
You got this.
Think outside the box.
Come on.
The letters 'N' and 'G'.
What?!
It's a trick question.
Never mind.
Argh. God.
Wait, wait. I need to rest.
Oh God...
Listen, Matteo. We can't
rest out in the open like this.
We need to find cover.
There.
Oh yeah.
A scary-looking fort.
Why not?
Come on then.
Come on.
So, does someone actually
look after this place?
Yeah.
A husband and wife.
They hate me, too.
[beathing heavily]
If it's any consolation...
You're a better
Catholic than me.
[pained laugh]
He's here. Come on.
This place is
like a maze.
We can lose him
if we're smart.
Oh fuck.
Fuck, he's already
been here.
... and it looks like
he's got us cornered.
Yeah, so we
got to face him.
With what?
Some dust sheets
and a broom?
Oh shit.
Any ideas?