Hey!
[screams]
[strong impact]
[grunting]
[screams]
[piercing sound]
[panting]
That was my nanno's.
Been busted for years.
Damn.
Is this him?
Yeah.
They both gave
their all for me.
Now I'm out here just
trying to do the same for them.
A rosary?
You're Catholic, huh?
Mm-hm.
I'm a stronger believing
now than before.
Really?
Put it on.
We need all the
help we can get.
We don't know how many
of those fuckers are out there.
Doesn't matter.
I'm finding my nonna.
Do you always do
everything in those boots?
Pretty much.
I'm ex-army.
Even running?
Yeah.
We'd run for miles in these.
Fair enough.
So, what route does
your 'nanna' usually take?
Well, there's no 'usual'.
Sometimes she takes the
north trail, sometimes the south.
She says 'hello' to
her friends in Libitina.
Then she takes the other
trail on the way back home.
So which trail
did you take?
I took the north, but
there wasn't any sign of her.
Then we'll take
the south trail.
So how long does
she usually take?
Six hours.
She's fast for 85.
Jesus...
No wonder she features so
heavily in your pillow talk.
- Down here.
- Ok.
So, how long ago
did she leave?
I don't know.
She wasn't home when I
got back from your place.
So, she could be
anywhere on her route?
Jesus. As if things weren't
complicated enough already...
Shit.
What?
That's the car.
It looks abandoned.
Yeah well, 'looks'
isn't good enough.
So, what do
you want to do?