A podcast.
Play this week's episode
of the Chase Peters show.
Sure.
I'm Chase Peters and you're
listening to 'Motivate The State'.
Today's guest is the lady
who made you tougher.
Zanna Hendricks.
Thank you for
having me, Chase.
Pleasure's all mine. Let's get
right into your new ebook:
'Nice Is A Vice'.
Now, what's wrong
with being nice?
On the face
of it, nothing.
But I mean, every
idealist preaches
having empathy and
kindness for others.
- Well, of course we do.
- But nice girls and guys and theys,
they finish last.
... and I'm not saying
niceness isn't a virtue.
but I'm saying that
you'll get trodden on...
... by those who are
ascending to the top.
But what would the
world be without nice people?
A terrible place.
But I'm just saying
leave it up to others.
If you have real goals,
I think niceness
just hinders you.
Wow.
Hey guys, check out this fort.
It is incredible.
It looks like
something from a bygone era.
So...
... my question to you is...
... should I go in
and check it out?
What do you think?