[phone rings]
Eurgh... Brian.
I've been trying you
for the past hour, Zanna.
You know it's
past my bedtime.
Yeah, sorry, the
signal isn't great out here.
Weren't you supposed to
fly home directly from Thailand?
Well, I took
the scenic route.
You know you have
a scheduled meeting
with a competition
winner, right?
One of those
underprivileged, terminally ill,
whatever kids. You know
what I'm talking about.
Shit, sorry.
I forgot.
Well, I can't do anything
in person, can I?
Hm.
Yeah, yeah.
I know you.
That's why I
scheduled a video call.
The kid's on the
other line, please take it.
Brian, I'm on a run!
[sighs]
Zanna.
I need you to
take this call.
We don't want the
charity or the parents...
... complaining to the press.