There's only one way to make
sure he doesn't follow us again.
You've got the knife...
No.
I can't do it.
Watch that wire!
Got it.
Hey, stop!
Zanna!
Stop!
Can you hear that?
No...
[distant church bell]
There is life in Libitina.
Here.
[distant church bell]
[church bell]
Everybody will be
inside for Sunday Mass.
We need to warn them.
Matteo, wait.
I want to tell
you something.
I don't remember how
we met or what we did.
I just...
... remember waking
up with you.
... and
I'm really glad we did.
Same.
The souls of the just men
and women
must be cleansed by
temporary punishment.
To be admitted into
the eternal country.
[doors opening]
Even the least pains in purgatory
are greater than what ever pain
is imaginable in the world.
The final purification
of the elect after death.
Matteo...
Nonna?
Matteo, wait!