Ok.
This one, let's go.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Jesus...
You okay?
Yeah, just not used
to sitting on jagged rocks.
Let me...
What are you doing?!
Ok...
You would risk
us getting caught
just to give me
a comfy seat?
Hey, can I ask
you some advice?
Yes, it's the one
thing I can give.
The next time
I meet a woman...
... what do I need to do to
make myself more...
... attractive?
Well.
I think it's about
mutual respect.
... and being your
own man.
Don't put someone
on a pedestal.
At least, not until
they've earned it.
But most importantly,
know your value.
You don't need
my advice, Matteo.
You're a very cool guy.
No.
No, I'm not.
I'm a coward.
Do you really
believe that?
Or is it just because
your buddy back there said so?
You're both ex-army, right?
Why was he
hating on you?
Not the same army.
I served America,
not Italy like him.
That's why he
called me a traitor.
As for me
being a coward,
I was discharged
with dishonor.
Why?
Desertion.
It haunts me every day.
[distant footsteps]
Shit...
He's gonna check
in here next.
He might not.
Do you want to
take that risk?!
What else can we do?!
Don't move...