Ok.
I'm gonna keep a safe
distance and distract him.
I will rejoin you on
the trail. Stay there.
- How?!
- Sh!
Stay there.
No. Zanna, no.
What are you doing?!
- Matteo!
- Woah!
Let's keep moving.
Come on!
Wait, wait. I need to rest.
Oh God...
Listen, Matteo. We can't
rest out in the open like this.
We need to find cover.
There.
Oh yeah.
A scary-looking fort.
Why not?
Come on then.
Come on.
So, does someone actually
look after this place?
Yeah.
A husband and wife.
They hate me, too.
[beathing heavily]
If it's any consolation...
You're a better
Catholic than me.
[pained laugh]
He's here. Come on.
This place is
like a maze.
We can lose him
if we're smart.
Oh fuck.
Fuck, he's already
been here.
... and it looks like
he's got us cornered.
Yeah, so we
got to face him.
With what?
Some dust sheets
and a broom?
Oh shit.
Any ideas?