Yeah, you're right.
We don't know
anything, do we?
I can't even be sure
that you're not one of them.
- What?
- How can I trust you Matteo?
I helped you kill
one of them!
[panting]
Come on.
I'm so sorry. It's my fault.
I shouldn't have stopped.
It's fine.
He would've stabbed
us both. He was fast.
Come on.
Come on!
[heavy panting]
All right. I can't keep
up the tough guy act.
Please, can we rest?
Ok...
Ok... but just
for a minute.
[panting]
You've always
been a strong Catholic?
Not always.
I'm trying to improve.
I'm a coward.
Come on.
You're not a coward.
You were a soldier. You wear
those stupid boots all the time.
I was discharged
with dishonor.
Why?
Desertion.
It haunts me every day.
I'm sorry.
I really need something
for this pain.
Try these...
These are herbs
from the mountain.
They only grow here.
Well, are they any good?
Never tried them.
Now's as good
a time as any.
We've stayed too long.
Time to go. Come on.
Watch it. Watch it!
Come on.
[phone pings]
Video message
from Clifford Hendricks.
Hold on, slow down.
Zanna...
Zanna, oh my God...
Cliff's been in an accident.
We were attacked
and he defended me,
but they beat
him up really bad.
He didn't have any
money for a taxi,
so, we were walking home
and these guys just like...
... they just, like,
jumped us.
They're taking him
to the hospital.
They're gonna do
an emergency operation.
These guys that attacked
us, they were like sickos.
They wore like these,
I don't know...
... these skull masks.
Oh fuck!
What?
- What is it? What?
- Fuck! Come on!
Shit.
Go. Go!
Quickly.
Down here.
Go, go, go.
Argh!
I need more
of those herbs.
Shit...
Here.
Finish them.
Swallow it!
Ok, good.
Let's go!
Zanna...
Stay here.