Fucking hell. A beta like you can't
have risen very far in the army ranks.
Beta?
You know what a beta is.
The opposite of an alpha.
A follower, not a leader.
A typical nice guy. You.
Well, my nonna taught
me to be respectful.
Yeah, I bet she did.
Bet she also taught you any
girl would be lucky to have you.
[snorts]
Textbook.
[sighs]
Tell me about
your last relationship.
Come on.
Ok...
We met online.
It started great.
We were very different,
but opposites attract, right?
[chuckles]
But then she started telling me
too much about her past relationships.
How they treated her badly.
But that made her want more.
... and that wasn't a
red flag for you.
No, I respected her past.
I wanted to be
different and treat her well.
So, you just accepted
everything she said and did,
even though you
didn't like it.
I didn't want
to ruin things.
Right.
So, how did it end?
- She cheated on me.
- [laughs]
Many times.
Voila!
See, your nonna's right.
Women will settle
for a beta male,
right after they've fucked a bunch
of big-dicked alphas first.
Hey, I helped you.
Eurgh.
Don't do that.
That behavior.
You're looking for gratitude.
It's a prime beta move.
It's very unattractive.
What?
Aw, did I hurt
your feelings?
Aw, come on.
Say what you want to say.
I've been called it all.
A narcissist,
a sociopath, a gaslighter.
A cunt?
I know that car.
The road manager
and his wife.
[speaking Italian]
[gunshot]
[glass crack]
[gunshots]
Come on.