Oh shit!
[bolt hits tree]
[gunshot]
Hey, help me!
Shit!
No, no, no, no!
I'm friendly!
[gunshot]
Fuck!
I'm not with that guy!
He was trying to
fucking kill me!
[gunshot]
Fuck!
Listen to me, you idiot!
[gunshot]
[fearful gasps]
Oh shit...
Fuck!
I can't!
Are you ok?
Go. Go get her.
[ominous music]
Hey!
Hey, come back here!
[knocks door]
Hey!
Come on!
What are you staring at?
Can you just...
Fuck!
Okay, look guys, I
don't want any trouble.
- [door opens]
- What are you doing?!
Get off of me!
[door closes]
- [boiling water sizzling]
- Oh! Ah!
You look too young
to be from Libitina.
[speaking Italian]
Look, I don't know
what you just said but...
... that's my phone.
Daughter says it
belongs to her.
You tried to steal it, outsider.
Well, your daughter is lying.
Shut up!
No, you shut up.
Enough.
[suspenseful music]