Yeah, you're right.
We don't know
anything, do we?
I can't even be sure
that you're not one of them.
- What?
- How can I trust you Matteo?
I helped you kill
one of them!
[panting]
Come on.
I'm so sorry. It's my fault.
I shouldn't have stopped.
It's fine.
He would've stabbed
us both. He was fast.
Come on.
Come on!
[heavy panting]
All right. I can't keep
up the tough guy act.
Please, can we rest?
Ok...
Ok... but just
for a minute.
[panting]
You've always
been a strong Catholic?
Not always.
I'm trying to improve.
I'm a coward.
Come on.
You're not a coward.
You were a soldier. You wear
those stupid boots all the time.
I was discharged
with dishonor.
Why?
Desertion.
It haunts me every day.
I'm sorry.
We've stayed too long.
Time to go. Come on.
[grunts]
Argh. He's too fast.
He'll get us.
No. Come on.
We can outrun him!
Leave me, Zanna! Please.