It's Matteo.
I came for you!
Our souls must suffer
and do good works
that break us of attachments
of sin and self.
Wake up!
This...
... is the word of God.
[footsteps]
Nonna, speak to me.
Matteo!
My brave boy.
What the fuck
is going on?!
So guys, I've finally
made it to Libitina.
From what I can see,
which is not a lot,
it's really beautiful!
But let me tell you...
These mountain
roads are crazy.
There's no streelights, nothing--
- [tires screech]
- [screams]
- [car crashes]
- [glass cracks]
No...
What's happening?
I found you...
... hanging in the barn.
In this moment,
you are on a middle plane.
A place which offers salvation
and purification...
... in the form of a test.
Bullshit!
Purgatory?
Yes!
It is a test you
have passed.
Yeah, come this way!
Thanks to your actions here,
you have purged
your venial sin of
Ah!
Cowardice.
You shall now...
... ascend.
... and Zanna?
She too has been tested.
To purge her soul
[gasping]
of her venial sin...
Selfishness.
[gasping]
I know.
[crowd cheering]
I ran...
... and I shouldn't have run.
You're a good person, Zanna.
You've done enough
to be saved.
Am I?
The kid's on the other line.
Please take it.
Argh, Brian!
I am begging you
to take this call.
Help!
Get out of there,
you little prick!
Please! Help me!
He's too fast.
He'll get us.
No. Come on.
We can outrun him!
Leave me, Zanna! Please.
[footsteps]
Cliff...
Cliff.
Come on...
My beautiful baby brother.
You were right.
Life is to be lived.
You have principles
but not rules.
... and you don't hold back,
but you're never out of control.
[ambulance siren]
... and you're kind.
You're so, so kind.
Wake up!
I am going to give you one
last motivational speech
So, you listen to me.
You keep fighting, ok?
[tearful]
Keep fighting!
Because you need more time
to spread your amazing energy.
So just keep, keep going.
Keep fighting... for me.
Please... because I love you.
Please. Please, wake up!
[crying]
What have you done?
What have you
done with him?!
[gasping]
Hey, it's ok!
You're gonna be okay!