[scratches hard]
[panting]
[phone pings]
Unopened video message
from Clifford Hendricks.
Zanna...
Zanna, oh my God...
Cliff's been in an accident.
We were attacked
and he defended me,
but they beat
him up really bad.
He didn't have any
money for a taxi,
so, we were walking home
and these guys just like...
... they just like,
jumped us.
They're taking him
to the hospital.
They're gonna do
an emergency operation.
These guys that attacked
us, they were like sickos.
They wore like these,
I don't know...
... these skull masks.
Oh my god.
No. Fuck.
Fuck!
Phone battery drained.
Goodbye, Zanna.
[distant church bell]
[church bell ringing]
Zanna!
Everybody will be
inside for Sunday Mass.
We need to warn them.
The souls of the just men
and women
must be cleansed by
temporary punishment.
To be admitted into
the eternal country.
[doors opening]
Even the least pains in purgatory
are greater than what ever pain
is imaginable in the world.
The final purification
of the elect after death.
Matteo...
Nonna?
Matteo, wait!