A beta like you can't have
risen very far in the army ranks.
Beta?
You know
what a beta is.
The opposite of alpha.
A follower, not a leader.
Typical nice guy.
Yeah well, my nonna
taught me to be respectful.
Yeah, I'm sure she did.
I bet she also taught you that
any girl would be lucky to have you.
Eurgh. Classic.
Tell me about
your last relationship.
Ok...
We met online.
It started great.
We were very different,
but opposites attract, right?
Then she started telling
me about her past relationships.
How they treated her badly but
that made her love them more.
... and that wasn't
a red flag to you.
I respected her past.
I wanted to be
different and treat her well.
So, you just let her
say and do whatever
she wanted, even though
you didn't like it.
I didn't want
to ruin things.
How did it end?
She cheated on me.
- Many times.
- Voila.
Look, your nonna was right.
A woman will settle
for a beta guy.
Right after she's fucked a
bunch of big-dicked alphas.
- Hey, I helped you.
- Eurgh. Don't do that.
It's very unattractive.
Looking for gratitude
is a prime beta move.
It's weak.
What?
Say what you
want to say.
I've been called it all.
A sociopath, a narcissist,
a gaslighter.
A cunt?
Hey, I got a confession.
What is it, Zanna?
Don't be weird.
It's not a Catholic thing.
I just need the toilet.
We just came
from the farm.
So? It is what it is.
Well, we can't go back.
We can go through the woods,
or there's an old military battery
with a proper toilet just beyond
the perimeter, if you prefer.
All right, well, which one's
on your nonna's route?
Well, she uses
both, but uh,
it's best we
don't split up.